adsnetworkreview.com 2016-11-01

# Privacy Policy • AdsNetworkReview

**Privacy Policy for AdsNetworkReview.com**

At AdsNetworkReview.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy page outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by AdsNetworkReview.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, AdsNetworkReview.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser(mobile/desktop), Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies  **  
AdsNetworkReview.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of  **[adsnetworkreview.com](http://adsnetworkreview.com/ "Ads Network Review")** then you may contact us at adsnetworkreview@gmail.com

**Last Updated on: 12th May 2013**

### Share and Enjoy
